https://massageprogram.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Campuses in Haskell, Tinton Falls & Bloomfield, NJ
+973.839.6131
admissions@massageprogram.com
HomeAboutLocationsITM Haskell, NJITM Bloomfield, NJITM Tinton Falls, NJAdmissions RequirementsFaculty & StaffAccreditations & MembershipsJob Placement AssistanceSchedule a Campus TourProgramsMassage and Bodywork ProgramOncology Massage CertificationEastern Bodywork ProgramMassage Therapy and Personal Training ProgramMassage CEContinuing Ed Massage EnvyMassage Continuing EducationAlumniJob Placement AssistanceInformation for Out of State Licensing ExamsNational Massage Therapy AssociationsTranscript RequestClinicFinancial AidExplore Financial AidFederal GrantJobsMassage Therapy JobsProspective EmployersWork For UsBlogCOVID19
HomeAboutLocationsITM Haskell, NJITM Bloomfield, NJITM Tinton Falls, NJAdmissions RequirementsFaculty & StaffAccreditations & MembershipsJob Placement AssistanceSchedule a Campus TourProgramsMassage and Bodywork ProgramOncology Massage CertificationEastern Bodywork ProgramMassage Therapy and Personal Training ProgramMassage CEContinuing Ed Massage EnvyMassage Continuing EducationAlumniJob Placement AssistanceInformation for Out of State Licensing ExamsNational Massage Therapy AssociationsTranscript RequestClinicFinancial AidExplore Financial AidFederal GrantJobsMassage Therapy JobsProspective EmployersWork For UsBlogCOVID19 Privacy Policy
The Institute for Therapeutic Massage, Inc. wants you to know how we use and protect the information you give. It’s important that you feel comfortable using our site and filling out contact forms. Protecting your privacy is our highest priority. If you are asked to provide information to help us identify you, please be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this policy. This statement can change from time to time. We recommend that you check back often to view potential changes.Information We CollectTo provide the best possible user experience, we may collect information on our website information request forms, subscriptions to newsletters or messaging to admissions staff. All personally identifiable information is submitted on a voluntary basis and may include:Name and job titleContact information such as email address and phone numberDemographic information such as mailing address, interests and preferencesOther information that is relevant to the formWhat We Do with Your InformationThe Institute for Therapeutic Massage, Inc. collects personal information only when voluntarily provided. We use this information to send out information that is relevant to your needs. With multiple massage programs, various locations and resources for prospective students, current students and alumni, we plan to offer the most customized experience possible.Some of the things we may use your information for are:Internal record keepingImproving our products and servicesSending promotional communications about things we think you will find interestingContacting you for market research purposes (only on occasion)Customizing our website to fit your needs and interestsOpting OutAll users have the option to opt out from our newsletters. An opt out option will appear at the bottom of the newsletter or email received in your inbox. Simply click the “opt out” link and your name will be removed from our list. You can also directly reply to the newsletter and request to be removed from future communications.SecurityWe are committed to the safekeeping of your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access to your sensitive information, the Institute for Therapeutic Massage, Inc. has secure physical, electronic and managerial procedures that protect all data.How We Use CookiesComputer cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and web browser. Cookies remember specific information to improve the user experience, such as which pages you find useful and which ones you do not. This leads to more relevant content and personalized experiences. Cookies do not give us access to any additional information about you. Please note that cookies are only added to your computer if you agree to them.Cookies are used on our behalf as well. We use traffic log cookies to determine which pages are most popular and which ones are not. The data is then analyzed to improve our website. Some pages may be updated or removed altogether. Traffic data is only used for statistical analysis purposes and is then permanently removed from our system.Some web browsers automatically accept cookies, so adjust these settings if you want to decline cookies. While this can prevent you from enjoying our website to its full potential, we want all users to feel comfortable spending time on our site. If you choose not to install cookies, we are confident that you will still enjoy your time with us.
Locations
Haskell, NJ
Tinton Falls, NJ
Bloomfield, NJ
Info Financial Aid
Privacy Policy
Consumer Disclosures
+1 973.839.6131
© 2020 Institute for Therapeutic Massage - a New Jersey Massage Therapy & Personal Trainer School. Built using WordPress and EmpowerWP Theme.
